{
  "Tutorial": [
    {
      "prompt": "How do you sign in?",
      "answers": ["Using the \"sign in\" button in the left sidebar."],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "cd000b19-5dfa-48e8-b6d3-31cb7aa391eb",
      "solution": "Good work."
    },
    {
      "prompt": "How do you mark a problem for review?",
      "answers": ["Change the symbol to the left of the submit button."],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "cd000b19-5dfa-48e8-b6d3-31b7aa391eb",
      "solution": "Nice."
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Option 1", "Option 2", "Option 3", "Option 4", "Option 5"],
      "correct_idx": [0, 4],
      "id": "10ab00d8-95ea-4ec7-8cd3-70fbb85e9202",
      "prompt": "If you don't know how to answer a question you can click the orange button to see the solution. If you click the orange button and then the blue button the problem will be completed.",
      "solution": "You can always click the \"Solution\" button to view the correct answer."
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b93b-4c47-8f0c-117608f58e8b",
      "prompt": "Do you understand how to complete problems and how to mark problems you don't understand.",
      "solution": "Pick options 1 and 5."
    }
  ],
  "Expand Demo": [
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b93b-gsd4c47-8f0c-11asdfa7608f58e8b",
      "prompt": "Do you understand how to complete problems and how to mark problems you don't understand.",
      "solution": "Pick options 1 and 5."
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-bjgh93b-4c47-8f0c-117608f58e8b",
      "prompt": "Do you understand how to complete problems and how to mark problems you don't understand.",
      "solution": "Pick options 1 and 5."
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b93b-4c47dfd-8f0c-11760gfsd8f58e8b",
      "prompt": "Do you understand how to complete problems and how to mark problems you don't understand.",
      "solution": "Pick options 1 and 5."
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b93b-4c47-kjg8f0c-117608f58esd8b",
      "prompt": "Do you understand how to complete problems and how to mark problems you don't understand.",
      "solution": "Pick options 1 and 5."
    }
  ],
  "EC2": [
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b93b-4c47-8f0c-11asdfa8f58e",
      "prompt": "This is EC2 question 1",
      "solution": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
      "correct_idx": 0,
      "id": "33694418-b9b-4c47-8f0c-11asdfa8f58e",
      "prompt": "This is EC2 question 2",
      "solution": "Yes"
    }
  ]
}
